A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Council on the Environment, 1970-1988
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 32359], 1971-1979., Extent: 6 cu. ft. (6 boxes). (Box 1-6)
  - Federal Environmental Impact Statements
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], Proposed timber sale regulations, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], FS [Forest Service], Control of Southern Pine Beetle, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 29-30)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Beautiful Run Watershed (Madison County, Va.), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Blue Run-Marsh Run Watershed, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Buffalo River Watershed, 1972-1978 (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Catoctin-Goose Creek Watershed, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Cedar Run Watershed, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 36-37)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Clinch River Flood Control Project, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Contrary Creek (Louisa Co., Va.), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Emergency Watershed Protection Program, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 40-41)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Flood Hazard Analyses Reports, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Great Creek Watershed, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 43-44)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Indian Creek Watershed, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 45-46)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Little River Watershed, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Lower North River Watershed, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Nibbs Creek Watershed, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Pedlar River Flood Hazard Analyses, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], Pohick Watershed, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 51-52)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], South River Watershed, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 53-54)
    - DOA [Department of Agriculture], SCS [Social Conservation Service], South Anna River, Service Unites 2 & 10, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - DOC [Department of Commerce], Proposed listing of Atlantic Bluefin Tuna as a Threatened Species, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - DOC [Department of Commerce], Disposal of ship generated oily water waste, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - DOC [Department of Commerce], Coastal Energy Impact Program, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
    - DOC [Department of Commerce], Proposed listing of Three Sea Turtles as Threatened Species, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - FCC [Federal Communications Commission], Microwave Tower (Lynchburg, Va.), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - FERC [Federal Energy Regulatory Commission], Randolph Hydroelectric Project of the Southside Electric Cooperative, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Alternative Fuels Demonstration Program, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Allocation of Petroleum Feed stocks to Synthetic Natural Gas Plants, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Bath County Hydroelectric Project, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Bath County Pumped Storage Project, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Coal Conversion Program, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 13-16)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Coal Research, Development, and Demonstration Program, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Columbia Gas Transmission Corporation, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Cumulative Production-Consumption Effects of the Crude Oil Price Incentive Rule makings, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], East Tennessee Natural Gas Company, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Electric Power Facilities Construction Incentives Act, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Energy Independence Act, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Ironton Mine Strategic Petroleum Reserve Site (Ohio) (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Liquid Metal Fast Breeder Reactor Program, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Natural Gas Emergency Standby Act, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Oil Import Program, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Proposed replacement of gas pipeline, Columbia Gas Transmission Corporation, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Smith Mountain Pumped Storage and Hydroelectric Development, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Strategic Petroleum Reserve, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 30-32)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Synthetic Fuels Commercialization Program, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - DOE [Department of Energy], Transcontinental Gas Pipe Line Corporation, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 34-35)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Upgrading and expansion of the Falling Creek Wastewater Treatment Facility (Chesterfield Co., Va.), 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 36-37)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Hanover County Facility Plan, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Henrico County Wastewater Treatment Facility, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 39-41)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Luray Wastewater Treatment Facility, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Montgomery County Wastewater Treatment Facility, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Henderson (N.C.) Wastewater Treatment Facility, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 44-45)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Chlordane and Heptachlor, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Piscataway (Md.) Wastewater Treatment Facility, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Proposed revision to Ocean Dumping criteria, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Public hearing, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Radiation in the Uranium Fuel Cycle, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 50-51)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Regional Identification Guidelines for Solid Waste Management, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], State Underground Injection Control Program, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], WSSC Piscataway (Md.) Waster water Facility (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], York River Wastewater Treatment Facility, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 55-56)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Amendments to Federal Water Pollution Control Act, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - HEW [Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare], Chesterfield County Library, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - HEW [Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare], Sarah Bonwell Hudgins Regional Center (Hampton, Va.), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - HEW [Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare], Smyth County Public Health, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - HEW [Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare], Tidewater Area Central Hospital Laundry, Inc. (Portsmouth, Va.), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - HUD [Dept. of Housing and Urban Development], Creek Conservation Committee, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - HUD [Dept. of Housing and Urban Development], Jefferson-Clinton (Hopewell, Va.), Streets Park Improvements Project, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - HUD [Dept. of Housing and Urban Development], Newington Forest Title X Development (Fairfax Co., Va.) (Box 2, Folder 64-65)
    - HUD [Dept. of Housing and Urban Development], Downtown West Conservation Project (Norfolk, Va.), 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 66-69)
    - HUD [Dept. of Housing and Urban Development], St. Paul Development Project (St. Paul, Va.), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 70-71)
    - HUD [Dept. of Housing and Urban Development], Standardsville (Standardsville, Va.) Water Main Extension, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Negative Declarations, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Negative Declarations, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Negative Declarations, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency], Negative Declarations, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Deepwater ports, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Great Dismal Swamp and Canal, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Bureau of Sport Fisheries and Wildlife, Important regulations injurious wildlife, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Bureau of Sport Fisheries and Wildlife, Annual regulations permitting the sport hunting of migratory birds, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Geological Survey, OCS [Outer Continental Shelf] Order No. 15, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Geological Survey, Exploration of OCS Regulations, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Bureau of Land Management, OCS Sale # 43 (South Atlantic), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Bureau of Land Management, OCS Sale # 40 (Mid Atlantic) 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 13-15)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Bureau of Land Management, Surface management of Federally Owned Coal Resources, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Bureau of Land Management, Hard Mineral Mining Operating and Leasing Regulations, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Bureau of Mines, Disposal of Coal Mine Waste, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Bureau of Mines, Surface Subsidence Control, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], National Park Services, Science Museum of Virginia road access, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], National Park Services, Assateague Island, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], National Park Services, Colonial National Historical Park, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], National Park Services, Chesapeake and Ohio Canal National Historical Park, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], National Park Services, Cumberland Gap, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], National Park Services, Boundary change George Washington Birthplace National Monument, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], National Park Services, Doughton Park, NC, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 28-29)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], National Park Services, Peaks of Otter Sewage System, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 30-32)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], National Park Services, Proposed Rehabilitation of National Mall, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], National Park Services, Richmond National Battlefield Park, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Bureau of Outdoor Recreation, Off-road vehicles on public lands, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Bureau of Outdoor Recreation, Proposed Potomac Heritage National Scenic Trail, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 36-37)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Bureau of Outdoor Recreation, Proposed South Fork New River National Wild and Scenic River (N.C.), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 38-39)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Occupational Safety & Health Administration, Inorganic Lead, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Occupational Safety & Health Administration, Sulfer Dioxide, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Occupational Safety & Health Administration, Proposed Standard for Occupational Exposure to Dibromo and Chloropropane, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - DOI [Department of the Interior], Occupational Safety & Health Administration, Inorganic Arsenic, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 43-44)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Douglas Point Units 1 & 2, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 45-48)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Early site review for Nuclear Power Facilities, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Floating Nuclear Power Plants, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 50-51)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Floating Nuclear Power Plants, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], General Environmental Sitting Guidelines for Nuclear Power Plants, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Improving Regulatory Effectiveness in Federal-State Siting Actions, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Liquid Metal Fast Breeder Reactor Program, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], North Anna Power Station, 1970-1979 (Box 4, Folder 7-10)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Perkins Nuclear Station, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Guide for Preparation of Benefit-Cost Analysis for Nuclear Power Plants, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Guide to the Preparation of Environmental Reports for Nuclear Power Plants, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Phipps Bend Nuclear Plant, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 14-17)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Recycle Plutonium in MIxed Oxide Fuel in Light Water Cooled Reactors, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Reprocessing & Waste Management Portio of the LWR Fuel Cycle, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Statement of Regulatory Staff, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - NRC [Nuclear Regulatory Commission], Surry Power Station, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 21-24)
    - GSA [General Services Administration], Federal Building and Parking Facility (Norfolk, Va.), 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
    - GSA [General Services Administration], Virginia Heating Plant (Arlington, Va.), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
    - TVA [Tennessee Valley Authority], Policies relating to Electric Power Rates, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 29-30)
    - TVA [Tennessee Valley Authority], Phipps Bend Nuclear Plant, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 31-32)
    - TVA [Tennessee Valley Authority], Vector Control Program, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - DOT [Department of Transport], Federal Aviation Administration, Brookneal Airport (Campbell Co., Va.) 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 34-35)
    - DOT [Department of Transport], Federal Aviation Administration, Chesapeake Municipal Airport (Chesapeake, Va.), 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 36-37)
    - DOT [Department of Transport], Federal Aviation Administration, Concorde Supersonic Transport Aircraft, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 38-39)
    - DMHMR [Dept. Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Central State Hospital renovations, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - DMHMR [Dept. Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Eastern state Hospital renovations, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - DMHMR [Dept. Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Lynchburg Training School and Hospital renovations, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
    - DMHMR [Dept. Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Northern Virginia Training Center renovations, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - DMHMR [Dept. Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Piedmont State Hospital renovations, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - DMHMR [Dept. Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Southeastern Training Center renovations, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - DMHMR [Dept. Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Southside Mental Health renovations, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9-10)
    - DMHMR [Dept. Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Petersburg Training School renovations, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - DMHMR [Dept. Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Southwestern State Hospital renovations, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
    - DMHMR [Dept. Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Southeastern Training School renovations, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - DMHMR [Dept. Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Western State Hospital renovations, 1974-1981 (Box 5, Folder 15-17)
    - DMA [Dept. of Military Affairs], Blackstone Armory, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - DMA [Dept. of Military Affairs], Fredericksburg Organizational Maintenance Shop, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - DMA [Dept. of Military Affairs], Gate City Armory, Richmond Armory, Petersburg Armory, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - DMA [Dept. of Military Affairs], Richmond Organizational Maintenance Shop, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - DMA [Dept. of Military Affairs], Staunton Organizational Maintenance Shop, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - DMA [Dept. of Military Affairs], Virginia Beach Armory, Lynchburg Organizational Maintenance Shop, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - DMA [Dept. of Military Affairs], Winchester Organizational Maintenance Shop, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - DMV [Dept. of Motor Vehicles], Possible locations, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - DMV [Dept. of Motor Vehicles], East Richmond Branch Office, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - DSP [Dept. of State Police], Campbell County, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - DSP [Dept. of State Police], 1st Division Headquarters, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - DSP [Dept. of State Police], 2nd & 3rd Division, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - DSP [Dept. of State Police], 4th Division, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - DSP [Dept. of State Police], Capital Outlay projects, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - VPA [Virginia Port Authority], Facilities Bond Act, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Recreational Facilities Bond Act, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Accomack County Park, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Algonkian, Churchland, and Enon parks, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Big Stone Gap, Fisher Farm Park, and Herndon Park, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Southwest Blacksburg Bikeway Project and Appalachian Trail Right-of-Way, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Blackwater Creek Natural Area, Lincolnshire Park, Riverside Park, and Upper Potomac 5th Acquisition, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Halifax County and Gloucester Point boat ramps, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Multiple parks, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Buffalo Creek Watershed Areas, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Bull Run Park, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Chippokes State Park, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Crooked Creek Recreation Area, Grayson County Park, Prince William County Park, Occoquan Boating Facility, and New Market Recreation Park, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Eastern Shore Boat Ramps, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Goose Creek Scenic River Study, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Island Park-Legion Hall Recreation Complex (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Multiple parks, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Munden Point Park, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Multiple parks, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Nottoway and St. Mary's Scenic River, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Patrick County Parks, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Multiple parks, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Rappahannock-Rapidan Scenic Rivers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Rivanna River, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Ragged Island Marsh acquisition, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], South Run Park and Granby Bridge Pier, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Surplus Camp Peary Land, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Walrond Park, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Willis Robertson Recreation Area, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - COR [Commissioner of Outdoor Recreation], Yorktown Waterfront Improvement and Development Program, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - VTO [Virginia Truck and Ornamentals], Research Station Enlargement, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - VCVH [Virginia Commission for the Visually Handicapped], Virginia Rehabilitation Center for the Blind, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - VCVH [Virginia Commission for the Visually Handicapped], Storage Warehouse Charlottesville, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - SWCB [State Water Control Board], Atlantic Sewage Treatment Plant, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - SWCB [State Water Control Board], Chesterfield County Sewer Improvement Program, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - SWCB [State Water Control Board], Hanover County Sewer Improvement, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 67-68)
    - SWCB [State Water Control Board], Hampton Roads Sewer Improvement, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - SWCB [State Water Control Board], Nansemond Sewer Improvement, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - SWCB [State Water Control Board], Arlington County Sewer Improvement, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - SWCB [State Water Control Board], Washington Suburban Sewer Improvement, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - SWCB [State Water Control Board], York River Sewer Improvement, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 73-74)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Airport Runway Extension, Franklin, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Mecklenburg-Brunswick Regional Airport, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Mountain Empire Airport, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], New Kent County Airport, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Noise regulation, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Orange County Airport, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Suffolk Municipal Airport, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], U.S. Coast Guard, Chesapeake Bay Navigation Area, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Deepwater Ports Regulation, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], I-95 James River Bridge, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Entrance to Chesapeake Bay, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)